您好  我是谢尔顿·库珀博士
Hello, I'm Dr. Sheldon Cooper.
我是艾米·菲拉·福勒博士
And I'm Dr. Amy Farrah Fowler.
欢迎收看首次出外景拍摄的
And welcome to the first "on location" episode of
谢尔顿·库珀博士与艾米·菲拉·福勒博士之
Dr. Sheldon Cooper and Dr. Amy Farrah Fowler present:
谢尔顿·库珀博士的《欢乐的旗帜》
Dr. Sheldon Cooper's Fun with Flags.
奏乐
Hit it.
♪ 论旗乐无穷 ♪
♪ For joy and fun ♪
♪ 什么比得上 ♪
♪ There's no better manner ♪
♪ 三角旗飘扬 ♪
♪ Than to fly a pennant ♪
♪ 旗与帜 ♪
♪ Flag or banner ♪
♪ 填满我的心 ♪
♪ What fills my heart ♪
♪ 弄湿我眼眶 ♪
♪ And makes my eyes moist ♪
♪ 把一面旗子 ♪
♪ Sending a flag ♪
♪ 升上旗杆顶 ♪
♪ Up a pole on a hoist ♪
♪ 欢乐的旗帜 ♪
♪ Fun with flags ♪
♪ 哦  你可看见 ♪
♪ Oh! Say can you see ♪
♪ 是欢乐旗帜 ♪
♪ It's fun with flags ♪
♪ 欢乐的旗帜 ♪
♪ Fun with flags. ♪
各位观众可能注意到了  节目其中一个改变
As you may notice, just one of the changes around here
是多了驻场乐队
is our new house band.
还没搞清谁主谁次的乐队
Who haven't learned their place yet.
另一个改变是  我们在不同公寓给大家做直播
We're also coming to you live from a different apartment.
我与富勒博士在她的公寓遭水灾后
Dr. Fowler and I began an experiment in living together
开始了一段同居实验
after her apartment became water damaged.
这里是我们好友佩妮的公寓
This is our friend Penny's place.
你们可还记得她上过
You may remember her from our episode
"旗帜与不懂旗帜的人们"那一集
"Flags and the People Who Don't Understand Them."
本着同居生活的精神
So, in the spirit of cohabitation,
本集的主题将是两个地区
the theme of today's episode is flags of two regions
合二为一后的旗帜
coming together as one.
比如圣基茨和尼维斯[加勒比海岛国]
Such as the flag of St. Kitts and Nevis.
咱们来把"圣"余袖子卷起  好好认识"尼"吧
So, let's roll up our "Sleevis" and get to know Nevis.
这音效不错  但下次先问过我同意
Well, I-I like that, but next time check with me.
你们知道这旗子
Did you know that the flag
是由一位名叫埃德里切·路易斯的学生所设计...
was designed by a student named Edrice Lewis...
真不敢相信我会说这话
I can't believe I'm saying this,
但我们能转台看个新闻之类的吗
but can we watch the news or something?
很有爱啊  他们很享受同居生活
It's cute, they're having fun living together.
不知道她公寓修好后  他们打算怎么办
Yeah, I wonder what they're gonna do when her apartment's ready.
其实已经修好好几周了
Actually, it's been ready for weeks.
你这话什么意思
What do you mean?
工人提前完工
Well, they finished the work early,
但她一直告诉谢尔顿进度严重落后
but she's been telling Sheldon they're behind schedule.
所以她就这么一直在骗他啊
So, she's just been lying to him?
你也骗过谢尔顿啊
Well, you've lied to Sheldon.
但我骗他是为了让他滚蛋
Yeah, but to make him leave,
不是骗他留下啊
not to make him stay.
布达与佩斯融合成了布达佩斯
Buda and Pest united to form Budapest.
以前俩城市分别在多瑙河两岸  后来合而为一
现在是匈牙利首都
这就是为什么布达佩斯
And that's why Budapest
棒棒"达"
is the "Budabest."
上音效
Now.
好...
Oh, right.
先生们  感谢你们的贡献
Thank you for your services, gentlemen.
希望你们年轻朝气的摇滚乐
Now, I'm hoping to broaden our audience
能帮我们扩大观众群
with your youthful rock and roll music.
你还觉得自己有观众群  真是又萌又好笑
Aw, you think you have an audience, that's funny.
没工钱吗  屁都没吗
We don't get paid? Nothing?
连个三明治工餐都没有吗
Not even a sandwich?
要到晚饭时间了
It's almost dinner time.
有什么想吃的吗
You in the mood for anything?
我们可以去吃你公寓附近的泰国餐馆
Yeah, we could get Thai food near your apartment
顺便经过去看看修缮进度
and then drop in and check on the progress.
你会后悔的  那里可是工地
Oh, you don't want do that, it's a construction zone.
哪又怎么了
So?
工人会乱扔钉子乱露股沟  你不是怕有人这样吗
Well, what about your fear of stray nails and butt cracks?
我害怕的是踩到钉子
I am terrified of stepping on a nail
还有跌倒脸摔进股沟中
and falling into a butt crack.
所以晚餐到底怎么样
Anyway, how about dinner?
你要是愿意
You know, if you'd like,
我可以打给你的房东替你抱怨啊
I could call your landlord and complain.
谢谢  但是不用这样啦
Thanks, but you don't have to.
没事的  我可是抱怨投诉大师
Oh, I don't mind, I'm very good at complaining.
如果有奥林匹克投诉赛  我就会抱怨
If it were an Olympic sport, I'd complain about
这是什么傻逼运动  然后带着金牌回国
what a stupid sport it is and then I'd take home the gold.
有意思
Good stuff.
所以晚餐到底吃什么
So, uh, what about dinner?
是我的错觉
Is it me
还是你一直故意在转移主题
or are you purposely changing the subject?
才没有
No.
说到主题这件事
And on the subject of subjects,
你用的"主题"这个词  跟平常我们说到的
is your use of the word "subject" the same or different
一国之主的臣民[同词]是一样的吗
as when we speak about the subject of a king?
我感觉到你还在转移话题
I have a feeling you're still doing it.
但我觉得这个主题我无法抗拒
But I find that topic irresistible, so,
所以说  在古代的美索不达米亚
now, in ancient Mesopotamia,
一国之主把人民视为他的财产
the king referred to the people as his property.
我是说真的
I'm serious,
美国喷气推进实验室真的在研究
JPL's actually developing a robot arm
能在小星星砸到地球前就抓住它的机械手臂
that could grab an asteroid before it hits us.
所以他们拯救地球免于受末日般灾害的计划
So their plan for saving the Earth from Armageddon
就是希望一帮书呆科学家能接住球吗
is hoping a bunch of scientists can catch a ball?
如果都是要死  我还吃这么健康干嘛
If we're all gonna die, why am I eating so much kale?
你静得出奇  怎么了吗
You're awful quiet, everything okay?
我有点担心艾米
I'm concerned about Amy.
她最近有点怪怪的
She's acting a bit odd lately.
我  我就有点好奇
Oh. Well, j-just out of curiosity,
什么对你来说能算怪呢
what registers as odd to you?
她的行为举止
Her behavior.
我总觉得她有事情瞒着我
No, I have the feeling that she's hiding something.
要我就不会担心这个
I wouldn't worry about it.
她可能只是工作上有些烦心事
She's probably just distracted by work.
不管是什么事  这弄得我很闹心
Well, whatever it is, it's troubling me.
我吃不下  睡不着
And I can't eat, I can't sleep.
更别提我始终一贯的排便时间
And don't even ask about the consistency of my bowel movements.
你们听见啦  大伙们  不要提
You heard him, guys, don't ask.
她为什么要对我有所隐瞒
Why would she keep something from me, you know?
我连自己的肉体都跟那女人分享了
I shared my body with that woman.
还有收费视频网站的密码
And my Netflix password.
她害我推荐列表里出现了爱情烂片
They recommended Stella Got Her Groove Back because of her.
兄弟  听我说
Buddy, buddy, listen,
没发生什么不好的事情
nothing bad is going on,
她只是...
she just...
她只是不想让你知道  其实她的公寓
she just didn't want you to know that the work on her apartment
已经在几周前完工了
was finished a couple weeks ago.
我不明白
I don't understand.
她喜欢跟你住在一起
She's enjoying living with you
不想提早结束搬回去
and she didn't want it to end early.
所以她欺骗我
So, she's deceiving me
是为了能跟我多待一段时间
in order to spend more time with me.
是的
Yes.
我真是既开心又伤心呀
Well, I feel both flattered and hurt.
就像别人说我长得像
Like when people say I look like
《圣诞夜惊魂》里面那个骷髅人
that skeleton from Nightmare Before Christmas.
天啊  终于知道你像谁了
Oh my God, that's who you look like.
谢尔顿  没什么大不了的
Sheldon, this is not a big deal.
只是一个善意的小谎言  人人都会这样
It's a little white lie, everyone does it.
我就不会
Not me,
我在所有感情里都是百分之百的诚实
I'm a 100% honest in all of my relationships.
单身狗的生活有多凄惨来着
And how single are you right now?
独自坐在马桶上吃蛋糕的那种凄惨
Eating-cake-on-the-toilet single.
我无法容忍感情里出现欺骗
Well, I won't tolerate deception in my relationship.
我无别选择  唯有跟她对质
I have no choice but to confront her.
千万别  你手里握着一张王牌啊
Don't do that, you've got gold here.
先收好了  等哪天换你做错事了
Hang onto it until you're in trouble
然后你就...  把这事甩她脸上
and then... throw it in her face.
什么  你为什么要教他这个
What? Why would you tell him that?
这个建议太烂了
That's terrible advice.
所以你不会想抓住佩妮的任何把柄吗
So you wouldn't want to have anything on Penny?
当然不想
Well, of course not.
那么假设我现在手握一些把柄...
So, if I actually know something right now...
我还真有呢...
and I do...
你不会想要我告诉你吗
...you don't want me to tell you?
不想
Pfft, no.
我知道你内心是"想"的
I'll take that as a "Yes."
她正悄悄地把你的藏品收起来
She's secretly been moving your collectibles into storage
一次收一点  而你一直没察觉
a little at a time and you haven't noticed.
开什么玩笑
Are you kidding me?
是这样的  我都知道好几周了
See, I've known that for weeks,
但我一直在等  等一个时机
but, you know, I waited till the moment
一个会让他最痛苦的时机
when it would cause him the most pain.
超人没了  帝国突击队没了
Superman's gone, my stormtrooper's gone.
你的每日克林贡语日历也没了
Your Klingon word-of-the-day calendar's gone.
我真想用克林贡语骂"靠"
I'd say "damn it" in Klingon,
但那个词是在下个月的日历上
but that wasn't until next month.
是"酷瓦克"
It's "Khoo-vakh."
"酷瓦克"
Khoo-vakh!
她把我的沃尔多收起来了
She took my Where's Waldo.
不  他在那边
Well, no, no, he's over there.
对哦  在那里
Oh, yeah, there he is.
你的公寓到底是什么回事呀
So, what's the deal with your apartment?
为什么要修这么久
Why's it taking so long?
干板墙的问题
Um, it was a drywall problem.
不会吧  怎么了
Oh, no, what happened?
干板墙湿了
Well, the drywall got wet,
没人会想要湿的干板墙
and you do not want wet drywall
因为干板墙湿了  它会变成...
because when drywall gets wet, it's really more...
湿墙吗
Wet wall?
或是潮湿的墙  反正都不好
Or damp wall, just as bad. Mm.
那干嘛不直接多弄点干板墙就好啦
So why don't they just get more drywall?
工人去买了
Well, they went to get some,
但卖墙的那个女人说
but the woman at the wall store
墙面正在打折  让工人们等等
said it was going on sale and they should wait
-因为...  -你扯够了没
- because the savings... - Okay, are you done?
伯纳黛特告诉我你的公寓已经完工了
Bernadette told me your apartment's ready.
本来在湿墙那里我就想打住  可你一直问问问
I was done at wet wall, but you wouldn't let it go.
谢尔顿真的相信你扯的屁话吗
But is Sheldon really believing all this crap?
他开始质疑  但我故意朝他打喷嚏
Well, he started to question it, but then I fake sneezed on him
他赶紧冲去洗澡了
and he ran to take a shower.
拜托别说了  我已经很内疚
Please don't say anything, I feel terrible about this.
别担心  我不会
Oh, don't worry, I won't.
谢谢
Thanks.
-"卖墙那个女人"  -别问了
- "The woman at the wall store?" - Let it go!
你会当面质问佩妮这事吗
Are you going to confront Penny?
最后肯定会啊
Eventually, I guess.
尽管我有点好奇她觉得自己可以
Although, I am kind of curious how long she thinks
这样悄悄藏我东西多久不被我发现
she can keep hiding my stuff without me knowing.
或许不跟她们对质
You know, perhaps instead of confronting them,
我们可以看看她们这张谎言网可以织多大
we should see how far they're willing to spin their tangled webs.
就像以前放在你桌面上的
Like that Spider-Man action figure
蜘蛛侠活动人偶
that used to be on your desk.
天啊  我真是瞎了眼
Oh, my God, I'm going blind.
饭买回来啦
Hi. Food's here.
太好了
Excellent.
我好饿啊
I'm very hungry.
说到这事
Yeah, speaking of which,
你的公寓是怎么回事
what's going on with your apartment?
工人还在修啊
Oh, uh, they're still working on it.
有意思
Interesting.
非常有意思
Very interesting.
是啊  我们去买饭的时候特地跑去看了
Yeah, we swung by her apartment on the way to the restaurant,
估计还有一段时间才能修好
and they're gonna be fixing it for a while.
等等  你去看她公寓了吗
Wait, uh... you saw her apartment?
是啊  离修好还远呢
I did, still a mess.
-莱纳德  -怎么了
- Leonard? - Yeah?
你为什么要说克林贡语
W-Why are you speaking Klingon?
那你为什么要说英语
Why are you speaking English?
你们太荒谬了
This is ridiculous.
佩妮  你还记得我以前教过你儿童游戏语吗
Penny, do you remember when I taught you Ubbi Dubbi?
你们不准说鸟语
Oh, wait, stop that.
你才不准说外星语呢
You stop that.
够了  你们这几个
Okay. That's enough. You know what?
到底是怎么回事
What is going on?
好吧  我告诉谢尔顿艾米的公寓已经修好了
Fine, I told Sheldon that her apartment's been finished,
可你刚才却说没修好
but then you just said it's not,
所以我现在也搞糊涂了
so now I'm all confused.
佩妮只是在帮我打掩护而已
Penny was just covering for me.
我的公寓已经修好整整两周了
My place has been ready for two weeks.
你怎么能骗我呢
How could you lie to me?
她只是喜欢跟你住在一起
Uh, she's enjoyed living with you.
这就叫陷入爱河
It's called being in love.
那么你偷偷处理掉老公的私人物品
Mm-hmm, and what's it called when you secretly get rid
这种行为又叫什么
of all your husband's stuff?
啥...这不是真的
Wha... That is not true!
博纳黛特告诉霍华德  霍华德又告诉我了
Bernadette told Howard, Howard told me.
再说我自己能看出来东西都不见了
Plus, I can see all my stuff is gone!
比起我来  你更相信你朋友  朋友的老婆
Oh, so, you believe your friend, and your friend's wife
还有你自己的眼睛吗
and your own eyes over me?
你真的以为我不会发现我的东西不见了吗
You really didn't think I'd notice my stuff was missing?
你注意到你的钥匙链了吗
Uh, did you notice your key chain?
人家的蝙蝠侠呢
Where's Batman?!
你为什么要告诉霍华德我偷藏了莱纳德的东西
Why did you tell Howard I was hiding Leonard's things?
等一下
One sec.
你为什么要告诉莱纳德
Why did you tell Leonard
我告诉你佩妮偷藏了他东西
I told you Penny was hiding his things?!
我们聊到
It just came up
秘密的时候就说随口了
because we-we were talking about secrets and...
等等
Wait.
统统不准说鸟语
Everybody stop it with that!
我没有参与这些事
I'm not really a part of this,
我好好坐下来听吧
so I'm just gonna dig in.
我想知道你为什么要多嘴说我公寓的事
And I'd like to know why you blabbed about my apartment.
问你呢  大嘴巴
You're up, blabby.
艾米  我很抱歉  我不该乱说话的
Amy, I'm sorry, I shouldn't have said anything.
没关系
I guess it's okay.
抱歉
I'm sorry
我为公寓的事骗了你
that I lied about my apartment.
没关系
It's all right.
你呢
And...
我什么呀
And what?
下一个丢的就是你的巫师袍
Your wizard robes are next to go.
现在大家都把话说开了
Now that everything's out on the table,
你们俩还会继续住在一起吗
you-you think you two will keep living together?
撇开最近的事不谈
Despite recent events,
我的确觉得我们的同居实验
I do consider our experiment in cohabitation
得出了正面的结果
to have been positive.
你是在说你愿意和我一起住吗
Are you saying you'd like to live with me?
我对此持开放态度
I'm open to the possibility.
随便你吧
Whatever.
如果他搬到对面去了
You know, if he moves across the hall for good,
莱纳德就可以把你不喜欢的东西搬到谢尔顿卧室里
Leonard could keep the stuff you don't like in Sheldon's old room.
-问题都解决了  -真是个好主意
- Solves everything. - That's a great idea!
也许我可以把他卧室改成游戏室呢
Ooh, maybe I could turn it into a gaming den.
那可就好玩了
That would be amazing.
等等   你要干什么
Wait, wait, hold on, do what?
搞清楚  那可是我的房间
dort dort dort Excuse me... that's my room.
但你不住在这里了啊
But you won't be living here.
可那是我的房间
But that's my room.
-可你已经不住了  -可那还是我的房间
- word word word But you won't be living here. - excel excel excel But that's my room.
你们干脆先开始吃吧
You guys might want to start eating.
可你已经不住了
ppt ppt ppt But you won't be living here.
亲爱的  从你不付房租的那一天
Sweetie, once you stop paying rent,
房间就不是你的了
none of this is really yours.
可那仍然算是我的房间
xyzzz xyzzz xyzzz But that's my room.
可你已经不住了
zyxxx zyxxx zyxxx But you won't be living here!
谢谢你的理解
Thank you for understanding.
没事  我明白
Hey, I get it.
每个人都希望多和我黏在一起
Everybody wants to spend more time with me.
我就像是蚂蚁王国里的小糖人
I'm like a man made of sugar in a world of ants.
晚安
Good night.
Mm, night.
如果我俩继续同居
If we did continue living together,
我们还会住在这里吗
would it be here?
我不知道
I don't know.
有可能吧
It-It could be.
当然我们还有...
Of course there's...
还有你的公寓
there's always your apartment.
当然  我们也可以住在我的公寓
S-Sure, sure, we-we could live in my apartment.
我讨厌你的公寓
I hate your apartment.
抱歉  是你自己提起来的
Sorry, you brought it up?
算了  也许我们可以重新找个房子住
Well, I suppose we could find a whole new place.
你知道  从技术上来说
You know, and, technically,
我们甚至可以不住在帕萨迪纳
we don't even have to stay in Pasadena.
我们可以搬去阿尔塔迪纳
We could, we could move to Altadena...
或是其他不是以"迪纳"结尾的地方
or a place that doesn't even end in "Dena."
想想就觉得兴奋
It's kind of exciting.
我们随心所欲地做任何事
I mean... we could do whatever we want.
万一搬过去  发现我们不喜欢怎么办
But what if we move and we don't like it?
万一楼里有抽烟的呢
What if there's a smoker in the building?
或者宠物
Or pets?
兴许还有霉菌
Or there could be mold.
还有可能有交通噪音
There could be traffic noise.
我还要学新的公交路线
I'm gonna have to learn a whole new bus route.
你是把《星际迷航》的主题曲
Are you trying to soothe me
当摇篮曲哼  来安抚我吗
by singing the Star Trek theme as a lullaby?
对
Yes.
我又不是小孩了  别这样
I'm not a child, don't do that.
抱歉
Sorry.
你知道《2001太空漫游》吗
Do you know 2001: A Space Odyssey?
对的  这才够抚慰人心
All right, now that's soothing.
我懂的  这里还是我的房间
Look, I-I get it, this is still my room;
我们还没真正把这里变成你的房间
we haven't really made it yours.
谢谢
Thank you.
所以我给你买了粉红战士
Which is why I got you this Pink Power Ranger.
你想放哪都行
Put it anywhere you like.
好  不过塞进去的时候你会感到菊花一紧
Okay, but you may feel some discomfort.
我开玩笑的  我希望你把这里当家
I'm kidding, I want you to feel at home here.
就按你喜欢的来装修吧
Decorate it any way that makes you happy.
你说真的吗
Do you really mean that?
真的
I really do.
太棒了  那我也告诉你
Great, and just so you know,
我不会把你的东西都扔了的
I'm not getting rid of all your stuff.
真的吗  你要留什么
Yeah? What are you keeping?
那蜡烛和你
That candle and you.
我的机器人海报怎么办
What about my robot poster?
只留一个蜡烛我也能过
I can make do with just the candle.
怎么了
What's going on?
一想到要从旧卧室搬走  我就浑身难受
I'm struggling with the thought of leaving my old bedroom.
你就不能自己在内心挣扎吗
Can it be more of an internal struggle?
我必须看它一眼
I need to see it.
我不在的时候
While I'm gone,
呼气不许呼到我枕头上
don't breathe on my pillow.
那我干脆不呼吸了可好
How about if I just don't breathe at all?
我的小宝贝最乖了
That's my girl.
作什么妖呢
What on earth?
这是怎么回事
What is going on?!
谢尔顿
Oh, hey, Sheldon.
我们把你的房间变成性爱地牢啦
We turned your room into a sex dungeon.
不要啊
No!
怎么啦
What is happening?!
好吧  最后一个问题
Okay, last question.
他穿的皮套裤  露屁股吗
The chaps he was wearing... assless?
能不能只关注我现在要做的决定上
Can we just focus on the decision I'm facing?
可以  不过要说清楚
We can, but for the record,
所有的皮套裤  都是露屁股的
all chaps are assless.
先生们  拜托
Gentlemen, please,
这个是重要决定
this is a significant decision.
现在我是要继续和艾米同居
Now, do Amy and I continue living together?
还是搬回去跟莱纳德住
Or do I move back in with Leonard?
你得踏过我穿露屁皮裤的尸体
Over my assless chaps you will.
这事情没那么复杂
This isn't complicated.
你爱不爱艾米
Do you love Amy?
爱
Yes.
你喜欢和她一起住吗
Do you like living with her?
喜欢
Yes.
现在你明白该怎么办了吧
Do you know what you need to do now?
明白该靠我自己想清楚
Apparently, figure this out on my own
因为你们一点屁忙都帮不上
'cause you guys are no help at all.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
我在当布里丹之驴
I'm just contemplating Buridan's donkey.
我懂了
I understand.
那我不打扰你了
I'll leave you be.
怎么  你懂这个哏吗
What, you're familiar with the reference?
当然
Of course.
让·布里丹提出的一个哲学论点
Jean Buridan proposed a philosophical thesis
说把一头饥饿的驴
stating that a hungry donkey
放在两捆完全相同的草料正中间
placed between two equidistant bales of hay
会因无法做决定而卡在原地
would be paralyzed by indecision
最终活活饿死
and would starve to death.
就是这样
Exactly.
我不希望你活活饿死  所以
Well, I wouldn't want you to starve to death, so...
给你根茄子
...here's an eggplant.
谢谢
Thank you.
知道吗  有人说布里丹
You know, some people believe that Buridan
是抄袭亚里士多德
was plagiarizing Aristotle.
是吗
Really?
不过在亚里士多德的例子里
Although, in Aristotle's example,
说的是一个口渴与饥饿程度相等的人
he proposed an equally hungry and thirsty man
在食物和水之间犹豫不决
caught between food and drink.
不知道这和十二世纪的
Yeah, I wonder if that's related
波斯哲学家安萨里提出的
to the 12th century Persian philosopher, al-Ghazali
一个男人在两个小妞中犹豫不决有没有关系
and his story of a man caught between two dates.
你是在说安萨里是亚里士多德派的吗
Are you suggesting al-Ghazali was Aristotelian?
可他是最反对亚里士多德哲学的人
'Cause if anything, he was anti-Aristotelian.
安萨里反亚里士多德吗
Al-Ghazali was anti-Aristotelian?
天啊  真是知人知面不知心啊
Boy, you think you know a guy.
好了  睁开眼睛
Okay.  Open your eyes
看看你的新房间吧
and see your new room.
我知道可能有点过了
I-I know I went a little overboard.
我们随时可以改回去
We can always dial it back.
不用不用
No, no, no, no, no,
只要你对卧室满意
it's-it's important to me
我就开心了
that you have the bedroom you want.
对我的意义重大  我爱你
Oh, that means so much. I love you.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
往你的橱子里藏点东西  不许告诉佩妮
Just hiding some stuff in your closet, don't tell Penny.